How much will we charge off the sun in
one day in Costa Rica? You can see all
my batteries are at 53%. We are
currently charging about 410 volts on
circuit one and around 390 on circuit
two. It is 11:16 and you can see we are
at 75%. Not even lunch time and we're
already at 22% on a 60 kilowatt hour
battery bank. It's like 12 KW in the
early morning light and it's been
raining on and off. 12:26, 87% all the
way around. Don't mind the wiring, I'm
still testing. Got to scrap it up later.
It is 1:21 in the afternoon and we are
up to 94%.
I told you it was going to be full by
3:00. They're going to be full by 2:00
and to go to Greece. Totes my goats. A
man with a goat is no joke. It is 3:21
and we are sitting at 99%.
A note about MPPT chargers, they slow
down at the top. So it's kind of like a
bottle of water, so if you fill the
bottle up, you cannot exceed the top or
it'll blow up. So it goes really slow
right there at the end. A little fact
for you and also so I wasn't wrong cuz
they're not full by 3:00. It is now
4:25. I'm still sitting at 99% but while
we were waiting, I took the entire finca
off grid. You see the hated government
wires taped up up there, not in use. You
can see power going into the house right
now. Now for the final verdict. How much
power did we make in a day? It is 4:25,
sun's still out, 34.7 kilowatt hours. It
was raining this morning, it was a
little jumpy, really low there and now
35 kilowatt hours in one day on a house
that only uses 30 KW a month. It's
insane. Guys, I did it. I actually did
it. This house is off grid. You see me
taking energy from the sun enough every
day to last an entire month. Well,
that's one hard question answered for
the day. Now for an even harder one. How
am I going to give all this excess
energy to Costa Ricans for free? Another
day, another video, Mcletus.